Many years ago, mankind faced a divine fury.
In an event known as the Day of the Cataclysm,
our entire world was burned.
The fire raged with an intensity
that threatened to reduce mankind to ash.
The places they lived, the languages they spoke,
the culture they had built,
none could escape its wrath.
This is Yona.
Yes, that's right.
He's still cut off from most of Company 8.
No signs of movement from the two of them so far,
but it's a matter of time.
Shinra Kusakabe and Commander Shou
will make their second contact.
All shall transpire as the evangelist foresaw,
Latom.
The show is just getting started.
I think I'll try to find a place to spectate from.
I'll come too.
Don't sneak up on me like that!
You startled me, Haumea!
A person with an Adola Burst who isn't me or Shou
has come here, right?
I feel like it's finally happening.
Yes, after nearly two centuries on the solar calendar,
I dare say the evangelist will be pleased.
The Adola Burst is known to some as the primordial flame.
To some as the flame of perdition.
It's one of the world's greatest mysteries,
because it never belonged in the world that you knaves inhabit.
This is where the Adola Burst belongs.
Here, in this charred dimension of bones and black flames.
So, an Adola Burst is a flame from this other dimension.
But if they don't come from Earth, then how do I have one?
Tell me.
Because absolute power cannot be confined to any one world.
Yeah? What's that mean?
And as long as I've got you here,
is this place a source of spontaneous human combustion?
I'm seeing this through our Adola link, right?
What is it, really?
It's the underworld, Adola.
But you'd know it by the name it received from the first people who saw it.
Hell.
You look upon the evangelist, Knave.
The one who protects me.
Who grants me strength.
Take what you got and leave now.
You're wearing out your welcome.
No one here wants to see you cheer, yeah.
Think that you won from day one.
But the devil will come.
You know just why he wants you, don't you?
Your crooked desire left us in history.
Misguided, defighted, it's a part of the reason.
You're starting a fighter.
You're gonna watch it burn.
Try to save yourself like you always do.
Every bridge we bow.
You think it's just a burn it down.
Just burn it down.
When everything is gone.
You wish you only heard us out.
Heard us out.
Screaming, me, me, me, me, me.
Me, me.
Me, me, me.
So, you're the evangelist?
You're the one who's using those bugs to turn people into infernals?
We're back here.
Hey, Shinra.
You okay?
What's going on?
Did something happen?
because of the grace of the evangelist i am possessed of an absolute power you may have
an adola burst but you can't win he's stealing heat from the rest of the universe as it cools
the universe's expansion slows down that's how he's able to make time stop that doesn't
sound possible even within a dollar burst your ally has the right of it i cool the universe to
slow its expansion which lets me stop time so it doesn't matter how fast you can move shinra
if he can literally freeze time then you've got no hope of catching him i know it's a long shot
but that doesn't mean i'm gonna give up
damn it
no matter how fast you attempt to fly my power will freeze you in place you're a cocky little brat
it's no use he'll destroy you you have no hope of victory a knave like you could never best me
what did you say i called you a hopeless knave yeah you've been calling me knave this whole time
where did you even learn that stupid word here's an idea show some respect and call me brother
you've really gone and done it now let's do this punk one way or another i will catch you
you've got this big bro you're not my bro
let's get back to our game of tag now last time we tried to play was a bust you couldn't quite walk
yet cease your rambling it means nothing to me now start running show your brother is it and he's
coming in hot
i'm starting to wonder if you've ever done this before you can't hit the tagger shell it's against
the rules i have no intention of playing your foolish game oh yeah you're scared you'll lose
here's the thing i didn't come all the way down here to pass the time
hey there ready to play a game with your big bro
he forced a link with me
this is crazy i think you're getting even faster shinra
got pretty close but i was faster than i thought i'd be guess that messed up my timing
what are you doing
i see why show's ability is so strong it must be because he has such a powerful connection
to adola
an adola link i felt a weird sensation in my feet and then suddenly i was faster
was that because of an adola link too as for the evangelist who is that really or should i say
what
i don't need those answers yet i just need their grace or whatever it'll make me strong
but how do i get it
i've experienced adola links on accident more than once gotta make it happen
the way this is going i don't think i'm gonna last
severed universe
it's a matter of time before you collapse
twice now the emotions of another person have found their way inside me
first there was lieutenant conroe's need for help
and second was giovanni's bloodlust
i get it now those were caused by an adola link
up to now i've only been on the receiving end
but this time i'll be the one charging in
i'm telling you an adola burst without grace can't win
yeah i'm aware of that
hey shinro i think we should run
if this keeps up you're just gonna get killed
why
when it's this obvious there's no hope
why do you keep charging forward
because my brother needs me because even now we're still family
why do you place importance in blood
i don't know you and i'm not bound to you
the thing is there are people in my life who i can look up to
well if you think he's alive then so do we
we'll strategize around the premise that shinra's brother is with the white clad
we were talking about how weird you'd been acting
there's no reason for companies outside of the eighth to meddle in the eighth's affairs
i want to see the white clad stop for good so let's stop them together
until you figure out what means the world to you
i'll take your help
i heard about your brother's show
keep him safe okay
what's your point
it's that as your big brother i need to show you the kindness that's been shown to me
look i get it i'm no one to you show i'm just some random person who turned up out of nowhere
but to me you're more than that i was told that you and mom had burned to death
i didn't think i'd ever see you again
one more time if i could just see them one more time
i've repeated that wish my whole life
and now you're here right in front of me
so i'll be damned if i'm gonna give up on you now
your big bro's gonna swoop in and save the day
show i'm so glad you're alive
thank you
i want you to know that to me you're like a miracle
all i can do is move faster
he's gone
but this is my frozen world
nothing can move here
so where is he
another one
seems earthquakes are getting more common
i'm getting a case of nerves in my nerves
i hope company eight's doing all right
keep the chatter to a minimum please
right
apologies lieutenant anyongo
sorry to call you out of retirement
after reka's betrayal you had no choice
and if you're still at the front i may as well fight with you
how's that right eye of yours feel
do all these recent earthquakes mean what i think
i failed that shinra kid i wanted him to stay out of all this
where did he go
should i return time to its normal speed
no
it's too dangerous to go back without ascertaining his movements
all right
i'm at my limit
what's this
that was rough
don't think i've ever gone that fast
went right past you
i don't get it
how did you move all the way over there
if you don't know
then i must be getting a lot faster
this game of tag isn't over yet show
yeah i promise i'm gonna catch you
hi show
do you want to play a game today
how did i get that memory
through an adola link
tell me
a moment ago
how did you disappear
hell if i know
i was just trying to go faster
show couldn't even find shinra by stopping time
how could shinra have disappeared just by moving quickly though
when a body travels fast enough
it reaches a threshold that it can't withstand and falls apart
if it's traveling at ultra high speeds
it can break down to the level of invisible particles
no
once a person splits apart
there's no putting them back together
then again
commander show is freezing the universe
that's pretty wild
maybe with the absolute power
of an adola burst
reassembling a disintegrated body
isn't that implausible
how is this evangelist person making all of this possible
ready or not
i'll kill the universe before he even moves
that hurt
still need to iron out some kinks
commander show looks really surprised
i know shinra's crazy fast
but could he be faster than the speed of light
if a body goes past the speed of light
it could go back in time
it's possible
after he splits
his hyperspeed reverts his body
to the state it was in before
wait
but if he keeps on moving at that speed
he could create a mini black hole
and if that were to happen
he wouldn't only destroy the nether
he would probably end up wiping out the whole tokyo empire
he has no idea
oh i should warn him
it's the right thing to do
i know
and yet
my curiosity's getting the better of me
i can watch it all happen for his hand
i'm starting to figure this out
you had better dodge this one
or else you're gonna be it
as long as i use my power first
i can stop you
i'm a bit surprised that you managed to force an adola link
but still
you're nothing i can't handle
at least this fight wasn't boring
he broke into my frozen universe
oh
did i land a hit
this shouldn't be possible
how are you able to move inside my suspended world
and with a flame the evangelist hasn't graced
did what was done to me
back when i linked with conroe and giovanni
it was the strength of their feelings that did it
so i used mine to connect with you
and since you're linked to the evangelist
well
when i connected with you
i got some evangelist as well
what are you saying
that you stole some grace from me
you see how may it's finally happening
yes
his adola burst has been activated through a link with the evangelist
one might say
it's the awakening of a fourth generation
commander show might be able to arrest the universe's expansion to stop time
but shinra can stop time by moving faster than light speed
we have similar skills
have had you
i'm keeping my promise to mom
i will bring show back home
he's standing right there
i just have to catch him
i haven't got a clue what's going on
are you able to see it hamea or no
i can more or less
i wonder for every word or two that passes between us
how many blows do you think they exchange
i'm not even human and i couldn't say
so did you get me last
i kind of lost track
what are you talking about
our game of tag
which one of us is it now
you or me
ridiculous
you're a persistent knave i'll give you that
but you need to accept i'm not your brother
why are you getting such an attitude
rebellious face
don't show up from nowhere
and pretend we're family
doing great bro keep it up
if you catch me i'll give you a treat
what's this has your speed begun to drop off
not a chance
i can do this all day
it looks like you've all but overheated
it's over
i'm taking you to the evangelist
we have need of your adola burst
damn it
chenra
wait a sec
you need to stop fighting right now
if you get overheated while using your fire
there's no undoing the damage it'll cause
you've gotta listen to me
whenever you move fast enough to stop time
your body disintegrates
in that moment you die
you think i've been dying
you use your flames to accelerate to the speed of light
that's how you're stopping time
but that tears up your body
breaks it into subatomic particles
then by accelerating past the speed of light
those particles go back in time
that's how you've been reforming yourself
but if you overheat in the middle of that process
then you'll actually die
in a way you can't come back from
you're saying i could die for real
what's so amusing
that grin turns my stomach
give it a rest will you
it's a nervous tick
or
it was before
but i don't feel nervous at all right now
i guess i'm just happy to be playing with you
stop putting things into my head
these visions disgust me
don't do it xinra
you won't be able to come back this time
i will come back
because i refuse to leave you alone
you hear me
if i left you to pin for yourself again
then what kind of big brother would i be
i love you
lleguez
belong in the next video
year
you
blah
i love you
yeah
Let's go.